girlschase.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy | Girls Chase

Read the following for your privacy information: 

Thanks for visiting GirlsChase.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use any personal information collected at this site. Please read through this privacy policy before you use this site or submit any personal information. By using this site, you accept the practices detailed in this privacy policy.

These practices are subject to change; any changes made will be posted and will only occur going forward, not retroactively. You are encouraged to review this privacy policy each time you visit GirlsChase.com to make sure you understand how any personal information submitted by you will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this site only. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

### **Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is **only** used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

###  **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

GirlsChase.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

###  **Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. Your personal information is **never** provided to other companies for marketing purposes.

###  **Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

### **Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us [here](http://www.girlschase.com/contact "Contact"). 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
